Thank you for watching!
Hi, I'm Takigami, a shooting star.
Well, this is a new project.
Well, actually, this is my room.
I'm serious.
I've invited a guest to my room and we're going to have a talk.
I'd like to do a new project.
But I haven't heard who the guest will be.
So my manager is calling them on his own.
Who do you think will come?
What's going on?
I really don't know.
I think there's some kind of relationship.
I don't know anything about that.
I don't think they would invite someone they don't know.
Wadakko and so on.
So, maybe Michiko Shimizu from Gifu...
But I'm sure you're busy.
Already?
Yes, it's OK.
Who is it?
Oh, here he comes.
Here it comes, here it comes.
Wait a minute. Which one?
I have no idea.
What is that, a shoulder?
Maybe it's a shoulder.
Okay, I'm coming.
Yoo-hoo!
You scared the shit out of me.
Oh, my God!
What a surprise! It's been a long time.
Long time no see.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Surprise!
I know it's just the temperature, but you're doing great.
You've grown up.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
You scared the shit out of me. Tacky.
Tacky, right. Tacky, right.
He's a senior.
You're being too loud. Close the door.
I have to close it.
This is not a studio.
It's my house. I live here.
I'm gonna be here for a while.
I have two years to renew.
It's a new house.
I'm closing up.
Welcome. What a surprise.
Mm-hmm.
Sorry to bother you. Wow!
It's the one with all the decorations I heard about.
Yes, yes, yes. It's my collection.
That's right.
I've got about three of them on Melcari now, so it's gone down.
Oh, I see.
Welcome.
Yes, I'm here. I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
You didn't know, did you?
I didn't know. I really didn't know.
Come sit here.
Then sit here. Okay?
That's great.
Thank you.
So, how old are you two now?
Right now?
I'm 26 now.
Wait a minute, you're 26?
Twenty-six?
No way! Because, you know, when I was doing the show,
How old were you then?
Like in high school?
I was just out of high school.
That's like 10 years ago?
What is it now?
Right now, Gilly.
I'm just about to graduate from high school.
I was about 18 or 7.
And then we had new students like Nakayama and others,
And they are in junior high school.
Hmmm...
So they were already minors in my mind.
That's for sure. Is it still like that?
Even now.
Even now?
What do you mean?
That underage feeling, that underage-like image. Yes, I have it. Oh, I see.
Because your name is also Ebichu. Well, that's true. It's complicated. Indeed.
Indeed. Junior high school student. I'm talking about junior high school.
Wait a minute. Mayama? I'm 28 this year, and he's 27.
Seriously? Because, you know, I remember, Mayama was the director back then.
That brings back memories. He said that for sure. I like you guys.
You're fast. You did, didn't you?
Yeah.
A lot of people were really pissed at me.
I was getting fucked up.
Oh, that's right.
With Kashiwagi, something,
A little bit.
That's right.
Oh, no,
Yeah, yeah.
I'm done with those guys,
I can't even... I can't even..,
I can't even talk to them.
Aya, you were wiping your face with a hand towel and saying, "I can't talk.
I can't talk to them.
I can't talk about this at all.
You are an old man.
I was an old man.
I guess it's a good thing I have a beauty regimen. Probably. It's possible. Not being too careful is my daily life now. Removing sebum. No way.
Maybe if you had strong skin. It was very strong. If it didn't, it would be stronger.
But it's all gone now, you know? You're an adult now. Yes, I did. I've grown up. Well, since we're here, I'd like to ask you something that I couldn't ask you back then.
I'd like to ask you something. Manager, please be quiet.
You are talking about your memories of the manager.
Yes, that's right.
It's been a while since we've talked there.
It's another corner over there.
This one is the main one.
Sorry. There is no wall.
The last time I drank alcohol was the last time I drank alcohol.
Yes, I did.
Once? Yes, once. At the party.
It was a long time ago. I think it was after the last episode.
I think Mayama was just barely 20 years old at that time.
Did we have beer there? Yes, we did. I had a beer.
That was also a big shock to me. Oh, but it is, isn't it?
That's right. I thought he was emotional and drinking beer.
Then, Mayama was like, "I'm going to live alone.
That's the time. That's right. Did you end up living alone?
Yes, I did.
But you lived at home for a long time.
And then you lived on your own. How was it? The first time I lived alone.
The first time I felt that I appreciated my parents was the moment I saw a bug.
Bugs? I really don't like bugs.
So, in the house...
There are no cockroaches in the house yet.
Not yet?
No. I thought for sure it was cockroaches.
No, I mean, what was it?
I don't know what it is, but it looks like a centipede, but it's not a centipede, it looks like a centipede,
It looked like a centipede, but it wasn't a centipede.
Something that looks like a centipede in Tokyo?
When I saw a noisy one,
Aha! I was like, "Huh!
It had some kind of vegetable color that I bought at the supermarket.
What kind of vegetable color?
It was a fresh vegetable color.
I was so excited when I saw it,
I was wowed by the color, and when I was trying to decide what to do with my sleeve, that was the first time I saw it,
I was like, "I'm going to do it, wow, which way should I look at it?
That's when you realized?
That's when I realized.
I'll probably notice it more elsewhere.
Like laundry.
I can do laundry.
It's done.
Oh, yeah?
Surprisingly. I clean my own room, so even if it's dirty, I live in it.
Don't you notice?
Because I've been exposed.
I don't mind at all.
When bugs appear, I'm aghast.
I guess.
Have you ever taken a break?
Living alone, yes.
When did you start?
Let's see, when was it?
Three years ago?
That's pretty recent.
I moved out when I was 24 years old.
That's late.
Late? In the eyes of the world, yes.
But my family was strict, so my father was strict. He told me not to go, so it was hard for me to leave,
But when everyone around me started living on their own, I said I wanted to leave no matter what,
Let's just leave.
That's good. That's good. I'll go out with a bang.
Let's go!
I'll have the three of us come back later.
Oh, two?
No, no, no.
Oh, two.
Ha-ha-ha.
So you were in high school then?
That's right.
That's when I was in high school,
That's right,
I couldn't go to the place where the director was,
But there was someone you liked,
Did you have someone you liked?
Someone you liked?
Uh...
Well, I... what about you guys? Did you?
No, no, no. Me? I can't ask that.
We're still working, in case you're wondering.
That's a question you should ask after you stop being an idol.
Really?
It's not that we're dating or anything. It's just that I like him.
That's for sure. Do you have a crush on him?
Do you have a crush?
But I don't think I had one. I like anime too much. When I was a teenager, I really wasn't interested in 3-dimensional people.
We included us. Only enough to be born and play with them and enjoy their reactions.
Were you interested enough to be born? I was interested.
I don't know. I don't know, but I'm interested enough to create a force.
You can't make it two-dimensional. It would break.
You have to do it in three dimensions.
No, I can't sympathize.
I can't sympathize with the three chiefs.
By the way, who is your favorite two-dimensional character?
There are many,
But I still love Sogo Okita from the work Gintama,
He was the first two-dimensional character that I fell in love with, so I love him.
So that's why I love him.
I just have a sword in front of me right now, and I'm a little excited. Yes! I was wondering about this!
This one, this one...
I've been a little too busy with the Corona Disaster.
I was doing kendo, but I can't even do kendo. I saw something. I saw something, you know, on Instagram, right?
He bought a sword and was practicing iai slashing. Hee! That's right!
I'll give you the sharpest tsukkomi in Japan.
With this, I was going to, um, cut off a life.
That's right! I saw it!
On Instagram.
I was cutting it off! And again in the street,
He said he had a sword.
He finally started holding a sword!
He started holding the sword of the Corona Disaster!
That's funny!
Shut up!
He's just trying to be a bullshitter!
Yeah, Yasumoto is something,
I know, Yasumoto was reacting on instagram.
I got the lead role!
Yeah, I think so.
Yes, I think so. That's great. So you've been doing yai giri at Corona Misaki for a long time?
Yes, I was. No, no, no, I'm not talking about that.
I was in love with someone.
So you were that kind of person, Mayama. Yes, I was. I was two-dimensional. What about Yasumoto?
But this may be a common thing among idols,
But, as an idol, it is not always OK to be in a relationship. I had a strong sense of duty not to fall in love when I was a student because of the image of love being forbidden.
I had a strong sense of duty not to fall in love with anyone when I was a student. I see.
I never really fell in love with anyone I actually met in real life, but I'm going to say it here for the first time,
I love Mr. Triplay, and the first male artist I fell in love with was Nissy,
I think my first love was Nissy. When was that?
When you were a student, in high school? I was in high school.
In high school. Sophomore year of high school?
I thought her singing voice was really nice, and that's when I fell in love with her.
But I shouldn't have done that. I'm a professional idol.
I was watching their music videos and thinking, "I'm an idol.
That's how it was for girls back then.
That's right. There were a lot of them around. At first.
That's right.
Do you say that kind of thing individually?
Oh, but we share.
Did you share it?
Yes, we did. If there was a character I liked or an artist I liked, I would tell them that I am addicted to that person.
When you are doing your "guess what" activities, don't you want to have an endless collection of your favorite goods?
Infinite collection?
Like this is how I collect them.
But, well, you know.
If you share them, for example, when there is a campaign at a convenience store, you may be able to get people to buy the goods when there is a collaboration with a member.
Yes, that's right.
I'll do it, so it's convenient to tell them ahead of time.
I was just saying that I like triple bait.
It's kind of in my mind.
That really is love through the screen, but
There's a rule that says you're not supposed to fall in love.
I'm not allowed to tell everyone.
I thought I was just being a child and being pure.
Don't call yourself pure.
But the principal said we weren't forbidden to fall in love, but I had to be reasonable.
That's the scariest part.
I'm not forbidden to fall in love, but I'm supposed to be discreet.
You have to make a choice.
So I guess most of you are a little self-aware.
Do you have plans for the rest of your life?
Yes, I do.
Here.
How old do you have to be to get married?
I don't know.
I don't really know about my personal life yet.
I don't know what I'm going to be like.
I don't know what kind of environment I'll be in, what kind of people I'll meet.
I don't know how far I can go in this job.
I don't have a very realistic idea of how far I can go with this job.
I have a lot of things I want to do in my work.
I have a lot of things I want to do in my work, so I prioritize them and think about when I will accomplish them and when I will start something like this.
What kind of things?
I'm currently going through the Ebichu activities, and I really like music, and I'm writing songs and so on.
You write songs?
Yes, I do.
Oh, wow.
I write songs, and sometimes I get to do a live concert once a year by myself, and I do my best as a solo performer,
Until I can be that energetic and sparkling.
I want to work to convey music to everyone.
I used to wipe my face with a hand towel.
I'm actually a beauty geek and a beauty lover.
I'm a beauty geek.
I'm a beauty geek, and I'm thinking that maybe someday, when I'm 30
I'd like to have more beautiful skin.
When I'm old enough to be persuasive...
I'd like to have my own original products.
I'd like to make my own original goods.
I'd like to do something like that.
When I become a grandmother, I'd like to work in a field.
I've flown a lot. I've flown about 50 years.
I have a lot of things.
So in summary, you want to become a Buddhist monk?
No, not exactly.
With a blue eye for beauty.
Yes, like a beauty researcher.
I'll study and research my favorite beauty subjects, and tell everyone about them.
I'd like to be able to teach grandmothers how to be younger.
I want to be able to teach people more.
YasumotoI've always tried to read the atmosphere, even though I can't read it.
He tries to read the atmosphere even though he can't read it.
I'm really using it to my advantage.
Once a year, on his birthday, he has a solo concert, a birthday party.
I rent the place and use it as a place to express my music.
I do a live show consisting mostly of my original songs.
I would do a live show with mostly my own original songs.
So that Yasumoto who used to do shooting star material with Kobayashi is gone?
He's not here.
No more?
No more dancing to Nishimatsu?
We'll do it on TikTok or something.
I don't care if you don't do it.
I want to do it! I want to do it so bad!
Yeah, I don't know...
I want to make my own image.
I want to do it!
Yasumoto and Kobayashi are like shooting stars.
That's so true! Shooting star school
Yes, that's right... copy and paste the material.
Yes, copying and pasting.
They study a lot and make videos and play them at live shows.
That's right... the questionnaire.
That made me happy.
He was trying to absorb us.
Absorbing us.
He was trying to steal parts of us. This guy.
But, you know, when Nagayama-san first started singing original songs,
Nagayama-san's first original song?
That's right. He also had me make the most of his live performances,
He was trying to steal Nagayama's idol image.
It's embarrassing. A professional stealing.
On the contrary, I was learning a lot from him.
Let's go back to Arson Yamayama's life plan,
I want to do this from here.
Not at all.
Not at all!
There must be something.
I don't know.
By the time you get to high school, for example, you'll be married.
No more.
Make an original cartoon?
Not at all.
I just want to be in the entertainment business.
I'd like to be able to eat the food I eat that day.
I said something like that.
No, no, no, it was the grasshopper and the grasshopper.
I'm always thinking, "Whatever will be, will be.
Why is that a little Okinawan?
You're not from Okinawa? Where are you from?
I'm from Tokyo.
That's totally different.
I just went to Okinawa.
Oh, I'm dyed-in-the-wool.
That's easy to understand.
It's so easy to understand.
My roots are from Tokunoshima.
I know your father's roots.
I'm from Tokunoshima in Kagoshima, so I have a kind of joint love for him on my own,
I hope to live in my grandmother's house in Tokunoshima someday, my father's house, when I become a grandmother,
That's all.
Well, you don't have to stay in Tokyo forever.
It doesn't have to be in Tokyo all the time.
Oh, I see.
I actually love Okinawa too.
Really?
I want to live in Okinawa.
Someday. I don't know. Realistically speaking. I have to stay in Tokyo for work and stuff.
But I'd like to move to Okinawa, and I've been watching YouTube and drinking at night waves.
I'll go into show business, and then I'll realize that I'm too old for this kind of thing.
And I'm like, "Oh, I'm too old for this,
I mean, aren't there other people my age who are working who have grown up a lot? They are all grown up. They are all so different.
That's right. They're all grown up. What? Are you thinking straight? Yes, for sure.
You have a good plan for your life. That's why I didn't tell you I want to do a side job.
Oh, that's why. That's it. Real estate.
So you're in real estate. I'm selling houses.
I'm selling houses. I don't know much about it.
I'm not selling the house, but I bought a condominium and I'm the owner.
The owner. And I have various people living there.
But when I think about the future.
I don't know how long I'll be able to do that.
Can I have one of these? Shall we eat this?
I want some!
Okay, here we go. Ready!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
All of them!
No way!
Give it up a little higher.
You said that before! Give it up!
I didn't expect all three of us to be together like this.
Let's just play rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper scissors.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
Too weak.
Aiko, right?
Don't you want to collect all the goods you like?
Don't you want to collect as many as you can?